

Bē handzel

naendzel



f.handzel@gmail.com

filip-handzel-7b653262

Filip Handzel



I am 25-years old. I live in Cracow. I'm interesting in programming, interactive media arts and design. I worked as intership this summer for 3 months in Owls Department as junior front-end developer mainly in Wordpress websites. I graduate from master's degree (10.2019) in Jan Matejko Academy of Fine Arts.

Education

Bezalel Academy of Arts and Design in Jerusalem (02-06.2018) Jan Matejko Academy of Fine Arts in Krakow (10.2014-10.2019)

Experience

Owls Department (7.2019-9.2019)
Polsat Report 2018, Insidelab, Baziółka
(HTML, SCSS, IS, jOuery, PHP, Wordpress, Gulp, Webpack, RWD)

Medialab Katowice (7.2019-11.2019) New media artist, interactive installation (C, ATMega2560)

Freelance (08.2017-02.2019)
Front-end family company (HTML, CSS, JS, webdesign)
Alek Jozefczyk portfolio (HTML, CSS, JS, design corrects)

Jan Matejko Academy of Fine Arts website (UX/UI Design, webdesign)

Code languages/frameworks/cms	Programs/other	Soft skills
HTML5	Terminal GIT	Work in team
CSS3	прт	Energy
Sass	Gulp	Respectful
Javascript	Webpack	Deal-making
jQuery	Photoshop	Creativity
PHP	Sketch	Adaptable
Wordpress	Pocket Adobe (Ai, Id, Ae, Xd)	Research
Bootstrap 4	Axure	Logical thinking
Vue	Visual Studio Code	Pixel perfect
Arduino	Slack	
C++		_
Processing		Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych zawartych w mojej aplikacji dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesów rekrutacji (zgodnie z Ustawą z dnia 29 sierpnia 1997 r. o ochronie danych osobowych tj. Dz. U. z 2002r., Nr 101, poz. 326, ze zm.)